fullycatholic.com 2013-05-05

# Privacy Policy

     Saturday, 01 January 2011 20:24 
     Christopher Phillips 
     Hits: 2441 

**What information do we collect?**   
We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or Date Of Birth. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * For you to gain access to our forums
  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To send periodic emails

**Do we use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  We use cookies to keep track of advertisements that are run on this site .

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**   
We do include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**   
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online **Privacy Policy** Only**   
This online **privacy policy** applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our [web site **privacy policy**](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our **Privacy Policy****   
If we decide to change our **privacy policy** , we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the **Privacy Policy** modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 01 Jan 2011

**Contacting Us**   
If there are any questions regarding this **privacy policy** you may contact us using the information below.

<http://fullycatholic.com/index/contact-us>

---|---|---  
  
Last Updated on Monday, 24 January 2011 21:41
